<resources>

    <!-- Base application theme. -->
    <style name="AppTheme" parent="Theme.AppCompat.Light.NoActionBar">
        <!-- Customize your theme here. -->
        <item name="colorPrimary">@color/colorPrimary</item>
        <item name="colorPrimaryDark">@color/colorPrimaryDark</item>
        <item name="colorAccent">@color/colorAccent</item>
    </style>

    <style name="AppTheme.NoActionBar">
        <item name="windowActionBar">false</item>
        <item name="windowNoTitle">true</item>
        <item name="colorPrimary">@color/colorPrimary</item>
        <item name="colorPrimaryDark">@color/colorPrimaryDark</item>
    </style>

    <style name="AppTheme.AppBarOverlay" parent="ThemeOverlay.AppCompat.Dark.ActionBar" />

    <style name="AppTheme.PopupOverlay" parent="ThemeOverlay.AppCompat.Light" >
        <item name="color">#FFFFFF</item>
    </style>
    <style name="DrawerArrowStyle" parent="Widget.AppCompat.DrawerArrowToggle">
        <item name="color">@android:color/white</item>

    </style>
    <style name="ToolbarColoredBackArrow" parent="AppTheme">
        <item name="android:textColorSecondary">#FFFFFF</item>
    </style>
    <string name="history">
            Royal Ambassadors is the name of a Baptist worldwide missionary organization for boys between the ages of 10 and 24 – an international organization found in many countries of the world, wherever there are Baptists. It is found on the continents of Africa, Asia, Australia, Europe, North America, and South America. The organization in Nigeria is Called Royal Ambassadors of Nigeria(RAN). \n\n In its mission education and ministry plan, RAN has a foundational Christian education plans for junior RA, boys between the ages 10 and 12; basic discipleship plans for intermediate RA, Boys from age 13 to 16 (or secondary school age); and solid mission education and action plans for senior RA, who are boys within the ages 17 and 24. The vision and work of royal ambassadors started in the united states of America in 1908 among the brotherhood commission of the southern Baptist convention, USA; and came to Nigeria as one of the world’s leading organizations for boys through the SBC missionaries in the 1920’s. \n\n The women’s missionary Union sponsored the organization from the beginning until 1954 when it was proposed that the men of the Nigerian Baptist convention should take over the boy’s work.  The situation that led to the proposal of Men and Boys department in 1961 which served both men and boys, then later became the defunct Men’s Missionary Union and Youth department, now known as Missionary Organizations Department since 1998. Royal Ambassadors National Executive Committee (RANEC) comprises of all elected national officers of the organization only; while the National Executive Council (NEC) includes all Conference RA Directors.\n\n The RA Marshal is the presiding officer in all meetings (of executives or general sessions). But the council cooperates with the MMU NEC through an advisory representative designated RA council Adviser; and operates from the MMU office, Baptist building, Ibadan through a denominational/administrative head of the unit. To the glory of God, RAN now exist in all Baptist associations, conferences and the convention, and is spreading its missions advancement tentacles to the West African sub-regions \n\n</string>
    <string name="worth">
        What would you say is the worth of a boy; In sin and sorrow, in service and joy; So much good and bad wrapped up in each life; To build up and serve or tear down in strife. A mine of diamonds, a bomb to destroy ? Depends entirely on who gets the boy? The devil, the world, and flesh make their bid: But what will your church do to win this “kid?” Some men have hobbies in which they invest Much time and money with real zeal and zest. But those who fathom life’s great thrills and joys Major on making real men out of boys. ORVIL W. REID. Southeren Baptist Missionary to Mexico</string>
</resources>
